I can't feel my body, cause I pop a lot of molly
Welcome to the party, bitch I'm bout to cut your body
Put you in this shit, we don't give a fuck about it
Bitch I'm starting right, bitch I'm bout to start a riot
Welcome to the trap, got my grandma selling crack
I make what you making when you're sitting down just moving packs
Make those bitches jumping jacks, like she with a acrobat
Had these bitches looking at me crazy cause I got bass hats
Ooh, drip, drip, drip, I can knock a wife a bitch
Dropped a million on my crib, now lil' pop is rich as shit
Ooh, and I still have my probation, poke a pillow, fill a mixer
You just broke and you just hating, all these diamonds on me skating
Man, I do this every day, spend 2,000 on some shades
I got bitches in LA, your boyfriend broke his diamonds